My mom hunts ghosts professionally.
No, no, no, no. She doesn't make money.
OKAY.
SHE DOES A PRO BONO FOR THE LOVE OF THE
GAME.
I'm not joking. SHE HAS A LOT OF GEAR.
SHE HAS BUSINESS CARDS. THIS ISN'T A
HOBBY. IT'S A REAL THING. PEEP.
STRANGERS call my mother and they're
like, "My living room's haunted." And my
mom's putting on her boots AT MIDNIGHT.
LIKE, I'M ON THE WAY. IT'S REALLY
SERIOUS. It's crazy how serious it is.
So, one day me and my brothers visit my
mom at her house and all of us are like,
"We want to know about what's going on,
right?" So, we ask her, we're like, "Do
you have one?" She's like, "What are you
saying to me right now?" We're like, "Do
you have it? Do you do you have a ghost?
We don't know how it works." And she's
like, "You're the dumbest people I've
ever met in my life." She's like, "I
don't hunt ghosts the way you guys hunt
deer or whatever." I'm not like I don't
have a cage and a duck call in a haunted
building trying to trick a ghost into
there. Like that's not what I'm doing.
She's like I'm an investigator. I
collect evidence. Me and my brothers
were like, do you have that? Right. Do
you have the evidence? She's like, yes,
I'll show it to you. And we're like,
we're here. Let's do it. And she starts
showing us her ghost evidence. Okay. She
starts with her EVPs. Now EVP stands for
electronic voice phenomena. And we all
know what it is from popular culture and
movies and TV and stuff, but like I'm
going to tell you what it is at its most
basic point because everyone likes to
like science jargon it or talk about
ghosts and weirdness or whatever, but
the reality is ghosts are shy so they
whisper into microphones.
It's the only possible explanation.
Truly the worst way to communicate. It
makes no sense.
You whisper and not even so I can hear
it now. SO I CAN JUST HEAR IT LATER. The
only way that makes sense is if they're
deathly shy, you know? I love imagining
my mom in a room with a tape recorder
and she's kind of scared and she's
trying to hunt ghosts and she's like,
"Is anyone here with me?" And there's
nine ghosts in the CORNER JUST LIKE,
"NOBODY MOVE.
NO ONE DO ANYTHING. THIS CHICK IS
SERIOUS."
AND then one of THEM IS LIKE, "I'M GOING
TO DO IT ACTUALLY." AND ALL the other
ghosts are like, "Don't you do it." And
this ghost just saunters up to my mother
and she's like, "Is anyone here with me?
what's your name? And she holds a tape
recorder out and he's like,
Josiah. And then he's like, all the
OTHER GHOSTS ARE LIKE, OH,
WHOA, JOSIAH DID IT. THAT WAS CRAZY.
JOSIAH'S NUTS.
And he's like, I don't know what we're
scared of. We're dead, you guys. I don't
know how it gets worse.
And then my mom goes home and listens to
it and she's like, sick. Ghosts are
real.
Yes.
So my mom shows us all her EVPs. She's
showing us all these recordings and they
suck and are lame. Okay. YEAH, THEY'RE
SO BAD. OBVIOUSLY ME AND MY BROTHERS
DON'T BELIEVE IT. So she's hearing
ghosts. All we're hearing is like, you
know, like, did you HEAR THE GHOST SAID
IT WAS HAPPY? And I'm like, I think I
heard a guy using the bathroom. I think
that's what I heard. A cat. I don't know
what that was. It's not a dead guy, I'll
tell you that.
So my mom is showing us her EVPs and
we're just we're poo pooing every one of
them, you know, and she's like, "You
guys are so rude. You don't believe."
And she goes, "I'm going to show you my
best EVP and then we'll see what you
have to say." And me and my brothers are
like, "WHY DIDN'T YOU START WITH THE
BEST ONE?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU HAVE THE GREATEST STORY OF ALL TIME
AND you're telling it to us backwards.
Ladies, get it together."
So, my mom shows us her best EVP. In
this EVP, okay, you can hear her and her
ghost friends talking. Sorry, I don't
mean to insinuate that my mother is
friends with ghosts. I forgot to tell
you that sometimes my mom hunts ghosts
with a crew of women who are also in
their 60s
and they look exactly like what you
think they do. Okay.
All right. I'm glad we got that sorted.
So, my mom is with her ghost friends and
you can hear them all talking to each
other and then into the microphone you
hear this crazy whisper really loud and
it says, "I want cake,
right?
Pretty scary."
So, me and my brothers hear this and we
go, "Oh, that sucks." And then all of us
stop for a second and we're like, "Oh,
no.
Ghosts might be real." Because here's
the deal. You can hear my mother next to
her friends. My mom has no like computer
ability whatsoever. She couldn't fake a
recording if she wanted to. I don't know
if you heard that story I told you
earlier, but my mom knocks out dogs.
She's what I would describe as a severe
woman. Okay? There's no possible way on
this earth my mom would be in front of
her friends and embarrassingly whisper
the phrase, "I want cake." If I did that
in FRONT OF HER, SHE WOULD KNOCK me out.
So now me and my brothers are like,
"Okay, that's weird. We're on to
something." Then my brother goes, "Hey,
do you have a video of a ghost?" And my
mom is like, "Yes."
And all of US ARE LIKE, "WHY DID YOU NOT
START WITH THE VIDEO?
STORYTELLING SKILLS ZERO
LADIES.
OKAY.
She shows us the video. In the video,
her and her ghost friends are kind of
milling about in the foreground, right?
And in the background, there's this long
hallway that goes behind them. And then
there's like a a sort of not very well
lit doorway that I assume they had gone
through earlier. Okay. So, they're all
talking in this room and you can see
this doorway. It's not very well lit.
And while they're talking, you see the
figure of a person lean out and watch
them for a little while and then he
suddenly leaves and never comes back. My
mom shows us this and we're like,
"Whoa." And she's like, "Pretty scary,
right?" All of us are like, "Yeah, that
was scary." And then one of my brothers
goes, "And you guys were sure you're
alone in that building?" And my mom
goes, "We're pretty sure."
Hey, ma. Uh, that was a dude. Actually,
THAT WAS A GUY. THAT WAS JUST A GUY. He
wasn't dead or anything. He was regular.
That was a regular DUDE. AND MY MAMA
GOES, "OH." OH, YOU THINK IT WAS A GUY?
WELL, THEN WHY DIDN'T HE COME BACK? WHY
DID HE just leave and not say anything?
Oh, I don't know. Probably because he
was terrified. How about that? How about
YOU'RE IN THIS BIG BUILDING ghost
hunting and he's probably the janitor or
something and he looked in and he sees a
bunch of crazy white women JUST BEING
LIKE, "SPIRITS, REVEAL YOURSELVES."
AND HE GOES, "NOPE. No way. Uh-uh.
I'm out." Yeah. I've seen this movie.
That's witchcraft. I know what that is.
I was like, "That's the scariest guy of
all time and he's never coming back." My
mom was so mad at me. You know, you
think you're you don't believe anything.
You're so tough. And then she's like,
"You wouldn't go to the most haunted
building I've ever been to." And I was
like, "I would anytime." And she goes,
"Next week." And I was like, whoa,
pretty soon, right?
So, here's the deal. I'm not scared. I'm
scared of being scared. Does that make
sense to anybody out there? ALL RIGHT. I
FEEL LIKE IT'S A CONCEPT MOST MEN
UNDERSTAND. I'm not scared. Scared of
being scared. So, I just don't want to
deal with it. So, me and my brother show
up to go hunt with my mom, right? We
show up at night. The building we show
up to is like this old building in the
middle of Utah. It's like this
three-story building. It's like 110
years old. Some wild west old bank. It's
huge and it's terrifying looking.
Straight up looks haunted. You know, you
ever see a building and you're like,
"Honey, look. Dead people in there.
That's a haunted building, right? That's
what it looked like." So, I'm like,
"Dang, not a good start for Shane." So,
we get out of the car and we're walking
up to the entrance. My mom comes out and
she's like, "There's rules while you're
ghost hunting." And we're like, "Well,
okay." She's like, "The first rule while
you're ghost hunting here, no one is
allowed to disparrage the ghosts. You
got to be respectful. Me and my brother
were like, "Okay." Yeah.
Second rule, while you're here, you have
to stay with me at all times. Do not
leave my side. Me and my brother like,
"Okay." She goes, "The third rule while
you're here on ghost with us, no one is
allowed under any circumstances to go
into the tall man's room."
Time out.
What? Both of us are like, "Rewind to
that thing YOU JUST SAID. THE THIRD
RULE. WHAT WAS THAT AGAIN?" And my mom
goes, "The tall man don't go in his
room." AND WE'RE LIKE, "STOP SAYING IT
LIKE IT'S NORMAL.
WHAT are you saying? What is the tall
man?" And she goes, "Oh, it's like this
10-ft tall pitch black skinny apparition
and it like grabs you if you're by
yourself and you can't scream. It's
really unpleasant."
WHAT? BOTH OF US ARE LIKE, "ARE YOU
BEING SERIOUS RIGHT NOW? CUZ IF YOU'RE
BEING SERIOUS, WE HAVE to burn THE
BUILDING DOWN, RIGHT?"
LIKE, what are you talking about, woman?
I was so mad. I WAS LIKE, DO YOU EVEN
LOVE ME? WHY'D YOU INVITE ME HERE?
You want me near this thing? I was so
angry because listen, I came here for a
Scooby-Doo adventure,
you know?
I thought I thought we would like hunt
some ghosts. It would turn out to be the
janitor. We'd all have a laugh.
I'd go home.
NOW I'M GOING INTO THIS BUILDING TO
FIGHT RESIDENT EVIL ENEMIES.
I don't want that.
I was so mad.
ALSO, WHY does he HAVE A ROOM? WHO'S
RENTING IT TO HIM?
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE? SO, I got here uh
this afternoon. I was walking around
checking out the town. Very nice little
town. But uh down where that little
farmers market is earlier in the day
there was a guy with terrible pausy
there which you know that should be
legal
and then I was there but the thing is he
and I were heading in the same direction
at about the same speed
but he was like 30 yard in front of me
and we walked like that for a little
while and then People started running up
to me going, "You're a jerk for making
fun of that guy.
I'm just trying to buy a woven basket. I
don't know."
I follow I followed that guy for a
while. I was like, "Whatever. This is a
This is a nice way to view the town.
And then he stopped and uh he started
coming back. So I was like in the lead
for a while, you know,
let him deal with it, you know,
like walking by people, that guy is
making fun of me.
My kids, man. I,
you know, this age that they're at is
fine. I don't mind it. But I like
babies. That was always my jam.
Anywhere from like one month to just
under two, you know.
It's a good baby age, you know.
I did make a lot of people nervous
though. You know, people were running
up. They're like, "Didn't everybody tell
you not to shake a baby?" Like, I'm just
holding them.
Don't tell me how to raise my kids.
My kids are all very healthy and uh uh
very tough, you know.
You know about like baby proofing your
house. You put gates on the stairs.
You put one at the bottom. Did you know
you also need one at the top?
If you don't put one at the top, the one
at the bottom just acts as a strainer
or a colander,
which maybe you didn't get the joke if I
used the wrong word that you didn't
know.
Some people are raised with strainers,
some colanders.
Just trying to hit the whole audience.
Like the balcony seems like colanders.
You know, it's cool though cuz you have
a gate at the bottom of the stairs and a
gate at the top of the stairs. We used
to just keep the kids on the stairs.
just raising little mountain goats.
It paid off, too. You We go up to the
Rocky Mountains all the time. They just
run up the mountain side. It's just just
so majestic.
Beautiful specimens.
I miss the stroller days, you know. I
love pushing my kids around the
neighborhood, showing them the world,
you know. But the thing is, when you see
me coming down the street pushing a
stroller, when you look in there, you're
expecting to see like a bucket of
doorork knobs or
It's quite alarm when you see little
Asian people.
Where'd you get that, mister? I MADE
THEM.
THANK YOU. THANK YOU. All right.
This is a lot of lot of moisture.
Thank Thank you.
It's uh, you know, having a disability a
lot of times people are like, you know,
I just think it's so inspirational that
you just you're just out in the world.
That's just you're so inspirational.
I'm like, well, thank you. That's really
nice of you. But I got to tell you, uh,
I'm a little uninspired by you cuz
there's nothing wrong with you and you
ain't done anything.
Now, here's a tampon. Go on.
>> I love it. I love telling jokes. Feels
good to laugh, doesn't it?
>> And uh you know, you guys have been such
a great crowd. I I actually brought you
guys some gifts. I uh I have a big stack
of uh
you know, I figure I'm disabled. I could
just make them.
Who Who am I to be hugging all these
goodies?
These placards are great, too. Not just
for parking, but if you get pulled over
like, "Oh, yeah, officer. I know I was
speeding, but did I mention
uh don't do that.
Don't do that."
Sorry, my lawyer said I had to say that
twice.
>> There's also a disclaimer on here. It
says if you're dumb enough to use this
as a real handicap placard, go for it.
That's on you.
And uh so on the way, I'll grab a
couple. Yeah, I I signed them and that
validates them. So
This thing, I'm telling you, man,
it's my nocturnal arm. You know,
sun goes down, this thing got stuff to
do.
I'm also pretty sure it's a sign
language interpreter.
I think it's Japanese. I don't know.
Maybe a little Jackie.
You guys remember from earlier?
I feel like some of you don't get
sarcasm.
This is a bad show for you
and I'm not being sarcastic.
Thank you.
I got to say uh over the years, you
know, being disabled, uh definitely
gotten a lot of material for that.
Very lucky that I'm able to laugh at
this stuff cuz uh you know, I've
definitely gone through some some tough
times. People can be real mean about it.
And I guess I never understood why
people were mean about disability cuz I
really think people don't realize that
the disabled community is the largest
minority group on the planet.
And it's uh cuz the thing is they they
pile us all together. So if you're
blind, get in the pile.
If you're deaf, help the blind guy find
the pile.
If you got one leg, hop on.
All right, I'll stop. I'll
That could be endless.
Whenever anybody's being mean about it,
what I think they don't realize is not
only are we the largest minority group,
but we're also the only minority group
that you can join at any time.
You're just one bad bike ride away.
Red Rover. Red Rover.
>> My second baby is my oldest daughter
who's about to graduate from the
University of Tennessee. She's 22. And
let me tell y'all, I know Ever Crow
thinks theirs is the blackest. But let
me say that she is a beauty and she is
smart and um she's done very well in
school and she's in a sorority and done
well with her sority and she's um
athletic and uh she's mean and um
we're scared to death of her. We walk on
eggshells around her. She's not mean to
other people or in public. She holds it
in so that she can come home and like
spew it out onto me. That's okay. That's
God's way. But
this is what I think happens when she
was a junior her summer between her
junior and senior year. I think that God
allows this to happen. And you little
girls that your babies aren't this old,
let just listen to me. All right? One
day they'll just turn on you and you'll
think, "Who in the world is this? Who's
coming down the steps in the morning? We
don't know who this is." I think that
God allows that because he knows that
you're about to let your baby go off to
college or whatever they're going to do.
And he knows that you're grieving. So,
he makes them just as mean as he can
so that you can let them go.
And I believe that.
That summer, the very breath that I
breathed out of my nostrils
made her so angry.
We were not allowed to eat cereal in our
own home because she couldn't stand to
hear us chew.
I don't mean to talk about her cuz she
had a lot on her. She had to empty the
dishwasher.
Stuff like that.
That's so hard.
Okay, let me tell you about an example.
When she was probably your baby's age,
your y'all y'all's little children, cuz
y'all are so cute. Look, they their
thyroid still functioning. Y'all still
got hair. Good for y'all. Um,
y'all got on little branches. Yay. Okay.
When my baby when my middle one when she
was in elementary school, I was so
blessed that I got to pick take them to
school and pick them up every day in my
minivan
and I would watch them come out, my
girls. And I saw them. They were in a
good mood.
I saw it. All right. They would be
gooseing each other.
and waving to all the little children
and the principal.
See you tomorrow. Okay. Then they they
come over to my minivan,
get in, slam the door. That middle one
would take her backpack and sling me in
the back of the head with it.
She'd say every day something like, "I'm
starving to death.
You don't have a piece of cheese in this
car?
Your driving's making me car sick.
I hate her. Why did you have her? And
the baby be sitting over the bank. She'd
be going, "Mom, mom, mom, mom, mom."
And I'd say, "What?" And she'd go, "Mom,
mom, mom, mom." I go, "What? I'm
listening." She could say some of the
craziest things. She said to me one day,
"Did Jesus ever have head lice?"
How do you answer that?
I said, "Well, baby, I don't
I don't know, but if he did, I know he
healed it."
And they'll be they'll be whipping each
other and telling each other how bad
they hate each other. And then my boy
would come out of middle school
He'd get in the car and say something
like, "You know, they're building a new
Home Depot up on 281."
>> Just as happy go lucky.
So precious.
>> You anybody you're with somebody who
snore, it just it mean it's just the
worst thing in the world. And and I
guess my head is where his is on the
other side of the wall. So you just hear
that snoring through the walls. You
can't do nothing about that. You know,
I'm laying there. I just hear m
I called his room last night. He picked
the phone up. I said, "Get off your
back." And I hung the phone up on him.
He was on his back.
Man, this is something, man. Who's
retired? By applause. Retired.
Yeah. Yeah. That's all right. I want to
retire, too, after the show. But that's
quitting. I want the
Yeah, I want the paperwork.
Yeah, I'd be like my grandfather. My
grandfather when he retired, man, he he
had like a a uniform.
You know what I mean? You didn't see him
in clothes no more.
The next day, man, you just saw him in
some boxing shorts, a tank top, and one
dress sock. That was his uniform.
He looked weird laying in the casket
with that on.
He just was strange looking, you know.
Still retired, you know.
Yeah. My uncle, he retired, man. He just
went on ahead and retired. He was on
disability for many years. Yeah. He lost
these three fingers on the job. He was
walking around like this,
you know. Yeah. Five fingers on this
hand. Left this hand in his pocket. Left
this one out.
I said, "Oh, why don't you leave this
one out and put the other one in your
pocket?" He said, "But I'm
right-handed." I said, "Not no more.
Switch it up a little bit, man."
Friend of mine, his his father uh he had
he he he retired from Tesla, you know,
and and part of his uh uh uh retirement
package, they gave him a top-of-the-line
Tesla on the way out, man. Beautiful
car. Oh my. This inside and out.
Beautiful car, man. And a friend of
mine, he had one, too, man. You know,
beautiful cars, man. Smart car, too. Cuz
like I said, a friend of mine, he had
one and he uh he he missed the payment
and the car drove itself back to the
dealership.
So, I don't think I want no car like
that telling my business, you know.
Yeah, that's a secret, young. Come on.
Yeah.
Getting older though, man. It's a
blessing to get older, isn't it? Yeah.
People don't like you, but you know, I
know I'm getting older. You know, my
things are tweaking right now. You know
what I mean? Like some of y'all too,
man. Like, you know, you don't know why
it hurt. It just do.
Like right now, my third toe hurt right
now. I don't
I don't know how you hurt your third
toe. I just got up out the bed and and I
limp to the bathroom. I said, "What did
I dream about?" Well, I hurt my toe in
the dream. I don't remember. Yeah, it's
just my body, man. It's just different,
you know? I just notice things are
happening. I was driving around the
other day. I was driving and I was
looking for an address and I couldn't
find it. So, I had to turn the radio
down so I can see.
The radio was up too loud. I ain't going
to find a thing up. This radio's up like
my eyes don't work when the radio is up
this.
I'm like, man, you do, boy. You do this
right here now. I do this, you know. I
don't know why I just started doing
that. My daughter said, "Your arm hurt."
I go, "I don't know.
I don't know if it hurt." I know some of
y'all do it, too. I know you do it, man.
Listen, man. Everybody, if you know who
Captain Kangaroo is, your hip hurts
sometimes.
You know who that is. You know you old
enough to know things ache.
So, I just sit through, man. I was in uh
my first time. I never been to uh here
in Pro. I've been to Salt Lake, man. We
was doing a big Halloween thing down
there. I like Halloween and and I Yeah,
I I trick or treat. I was 24.
That's free candy right there. I don't
understand. I don't know how homeless
people go hungry on Halloween.
All you got to do is ring a doorbell and
get some candy. You're already in your
uniform.
You got me.
Hey, get you some freaking a whole bag
of candy all week long, man. Other
people jealous of you. Oh, man. You
should have rang door bells.
Yeah. I I was I was 24, man. Yeah. I
would be up on your porch knocking trick
or treat.
Don't you drive a school bus?
Yes, ma'am. There my bus over there.
Just as a bus driver, I fig I'd come
over. I heard you had Kit Kat, so I
figure I get off my bus, come on over
here.
I used to love trick-or-treating, boy.
Trick-or-treating has changed though,
you know. Yeah. You said kids out now,
boy, they got to walk around with their
parents now, you know. And I understand
that cuz I have some grandsons. I take
them trick-or-treating. But I'm only
there so uh when the people open the
door, I can look in their house.
That's the only reason I'm there. Like
they ring the doorbell, as soon as they
open my head up in there, you know?
>> Yeah. I want to make sure it's clean up
in there. That's all I'm saying. You
can't get them dishes out the sink. We
don't want your candy. You can't
can't even clean up. You knew somebody's
going to come by here this evening.
My mother was cheap though, never bought
the whole costume, just the mask.
People knew it was me. I had the same
school clothes on. They knew exactly who
it was.
They knew exactly what it Yeah. I knock
on the door anyway. Trick or treat. And
Roman, is that you? I said, "No, I'm
Superman."
So, well, Superman, take this cornbread
skillet back to your mama and tell her I
said, "Thank you so much."
Walk around neighborhood with that cast
iron know how heavy that skillet is.
Cheap man. One year she told me keep my
school clothes on and go as a fifth
grader.
Remember my last year trick-or-treating.
True story. My mother threw a she threw
a black bed sheet over my head and and
told me I was a ghost.
Oh, maybe y'all didn't hear me. My
mother threw a black bed sheet.
Just draped it on. Pushed me on out the
door, man.
Almost got hit by four cars that night.
I remember that. I remember.
At least cut the eyes out. My goodness.
You don't love me. You don't cut the
eyes out the thing. Come on now.
I get back in the house. She talking
about go put your costume back on your
bed.
I thought I was Superman. I went as a
twin mattress this year. I didn't know.
What three of my friends used to do, uh,
what three of my friends used to do, we
used to go across town, uh, to the white
neighborhood cuz y'all always had the
best candy. Oo, y'all went grocery
shopping for y'all stuff. Y'all had to
go.
Yeah, boy. It was only like three of us
used to go though, you know, more than
three little black kids. We thought
y'all was going to turn that porch light
off on us. So,
three little black kids is cute. Four is
a gang. So, we not
trying to scare nobody on Halloween, I
guess.
Yeah, boy. Y'all had the good stuff,
boy. Whole snicker balls and rice
krispie treats. The thick stuff, boy.
Candy apples. You don't know what you
going to get in my neighborhood. We hope
you got candy.
Yeah. You ring the doorbell, baby. You
like pork and beans.
Yeah, actually I do. Go ahead and put
them in that skillet. You see that
skillet? Put them in that skillet in
there. You see that skillet right there?
Just go ahead and put them in there.
Tell you guys this about me. I am
married. I'm married. Celebrating 13
years next year. Yeah. Like that.
I love it, man. I love being married. A
lot of commerce they get up here and
they talk junk about their wives. That's
not me. I love my wife. I absolutely
love her. Here's the only issue I have.
Okay,
here's my only problem. After a decade
with the same woman, I thought I'd know
everything there was to know about that
woman. Wrong.
I learned new things about my wife all
the time. I'm like, "Recently, I learned
my wife's a magician,
and her favorite new trick is she'll
change the TV to some show I don't want
to watch, and then the remote
disappears.
She watches reality TV. Anybody here
watch reality TV? That's stupid. Shut
up."
Hey, I'm like, how boring is our life?
We got to sit around watching other
people live their life. You kidding me?
We're paying cable for this. Let's go to
Walmart and judge people. That's free.
I hate She watch the worst kinds of
reality TV. That's what I hate the most.
Like, she watched this one show uh
called 16 Impregant. I don't know if you
guys have seen this show. Young mom is
what it's called now or something like
that. Here's what happens if you haven't
seen it. Every single episode it's the
exact same. Some young lady upset,
pregnant, crying on somebody's couch,
usually not her own,
texting with the baby's father. And what
I've noticed while we watch marathons of
this stupid show is every single one of
these young ladies is texting the baby's
father on a cell phone in a protective
case.
That is the fourth most ironic thing
I've seen in my life.
Right behind the Hindu kid in a yolo
t-shirt.
A guy in a wheelchair singing stand by
me at karaoke.
And this lady in my mom's church who
sings we fall down but we get up with
the life alert necklace on.
It was a false testimony. Sister Karen,
sit down somewhere.
I hate it, man. My wife, she watched
this whole other series of reality TV
shows about Amish people. If you guys
seen any of these breaking Amish, the
Amish Mafia.
These are real shows. cuz I want to tell
her they're fake, but I can't find any
Amish people who've seen them to back me
up. So,
it's my word against hers.
She's so invested in the lives of these
people and like she's so interested like
she notices anything Amish now. If
there's an Amish store while we're on
the road, she wants to stop there. And a
couple months ago, we were walking
through the grocery store and we went
through the book aisle and in the book
aisle were these things called Amish
romance novels.
That was my reaction. Like, why why
would you do this?
Ain't it not like what you you guys
remember the old romance novels, right?
They had Fabio on the cover, all oiled
up, hair blowing in the wind.
Amish romance novels are a little
different. It's some modestly dressed
Amish woman on the cover. She's got on
her bonnet, but the straps are untied
cuz that's provocative.
The straps are just blowing in the wind.
I'm looking around the store. I don't
see any Amish people anywhere, but these
books are flying off the shelves, which
means which means every day people are
buying up Amish romance novels. They're
watching Amish reality TV, which means
there's a whole Amish industry I need to
get into as a businessman.
So, next year I'm starting the first
ever Amish soap opera. It's going to be
called As the Butter Churns.
Start a whole web series called Amish
Girls Gone Wild. There's going to be
Amish girls in hotel rooms doing crazy
stuff like turning the lights on and off
playing Xbox. It's going to be amazing.
Having a web shaw contest. I can't wait.
Time for spin the bonnet. It's going to
be awesome. So,
I do love my wife. She surprises me all
the time, man. All the time. A couple
months ago, she thought she was going to
do something a little special. She told
me she wanted to do a little role
rehearsal in the bedroom.
That's right. Yeah. So, I woke her up
late at night.
Talked about my feelings.
Oh, were you asleep? My bad.
Since you're up, I've been thinking
Got out of bed after that. Walked around
the house, got my feet good and cold.
>> Crawled back into bed and dug them in
the back of her legs. It was beautiful.
Here's what I love most about that joke.
Okay? Is that 80% of the men in here are
laughing and the other 20% aren't
allowed to
I don't know what he's talking about.
Honey, I love your icicle teeth. I don't
do I love being married. I really do. I
love being married. Here's the only
thing is, you know, when you're in a
long-term relationship,
when you're in a long-term relationship,
you have ups and downs. That's just how
it works, right? You know, and uh we're
in the technological age. So, here's
what I like to do, sir, is every time me
and my wife have an argument, I like to
Google it to see who's right,
wrong move, fellas. Uh, just so you
know, but I do love it because I
sometimes fall on this Google rabbit
hole and I discover things I should have
never discovered, you know, otherwise. I
discovered this recently. There was a
psychological test done a couple of
years ago that tells us that you can
tell the personality of the people you
live with all based on how they put the
toilet paper on the toilet paper roll.
It's a true thing. You can look it up.
Okay, in a nutshell, here's how it
works. All right. If you put the toilet
paper on the toilet paper roll and it
comes over the top for you to pull off,
that means you are a dominant
personality.
Now, if you put the toilet paper on the
toilet paper roll and it comes
underneath for you to pull off, that
means you are a submissive personality.
And that makes complete sense. In my
house, I put the toilet paper on the
toilet paper roll and it comes over the
top for you to pull off cuz I'm
dominant. Okay? And my wife, she puts
the toilet paper on top of the empty
cardboard from the last toilet paper
roll.
Show me who's boss, I guess. I'm not
sure.
They didn't cover that in the study.
Marriage is fun. Marriage is fun.
Sometimes little things happen that make
even even more fun. Like recently, two
years ago, we had our first child, a
baby girl. Very excited about that.
Yeah,
this my heart, man. I love that little
girl. It's amazing. You know, when
you're a guy and you find out you're
going to be a father, what you want to
do is you want to tell all your friends
that you're going to be a dad. And
that's what I did. I took out two of my
best friends and I told them that I was
going to be a father. And on this day, I
figured out how stupid my best friends
are
cuz they started asking me questions
that I thought were ridiculous. I'm
hanging out with my friends. I tell
them, "Hey y'all, just found out my
wife's pregnant. We're expecting. I'm
very excited. I'm going to be a father."
One of my friends looks at me. He goes,
"Joe, that's awesome. You're going to be
a great dad. That's amazing.
Congratulations. Uh, one question. What
if you have a gay baby?
I was like, well, listen. First of all,
I'm going to love my child no matter
what. That's first. Okay. Also, what is
a gay baby?
You ever seen one of those?
You ever been walking through the
grocery store and seen a baby crying in
the car? Like, WOW.
Where
You've never seen that? That's
ridiculous, right? I thought that was
the dumbest question I'd ever heard.
Then my other friend leans across the
table. He's like, "Joe, forget about a
gay baby. It's modern times. What if you
have a transgender baby?" I said,
"Listen again, I'm going to love my
child no matter what. That's the only
job I have on this earth is to give that
child love." Okay. Also, have you seen a
baby? Cuz if they don't have on the
right color, they can all pass for
transgender. You know what I'm talking
about?
You ever seen a baby with no hair, no
pink, no blue? Now you got to guess what
it is.
You feed them. You're like, "Oh my
goodness,
isn't it cute?
What's its name?"
Jamie.
That doesn't help at all. That is
a gay baby. That's what that is.
As a comedian, man, I travel. I travel a
lot, man. But I just hate that process
cuz it's such a You got to go through
the the TSA. You got to take all your
clothes off. You got to go after you got
to wait in line. The jet bridge. Oh, I
hate the jet bridge. The little, you
know, the thing you take the little
steps.
Boarding one, row one, main cabin one.
People with babies and mentally
challenged the disabled people, they get
to go first. I try to go first. Let me
go first.
I'm like, sir, what? What? Sir, ain't
nothing wrong with you. Okay, I go
first.
I don't think they ever say mentally
challenged. Actually, I don't think they
say that.
I don't know what's politically
incorrect to say anymore either. I
didn't even was that is that I don't
know. They got to send out mass emails
or something like I don't even know
cuz you don't KNOW. I WAS AT A SCHOOL
THE OTHER DAY AND I SAID SOMETHING LIKE
YOU CAN'T SAY THAT. NOBODY TOLD ME.
NOBODY TOLD ME. out the air that like
the commercial during the Super Bowl or
something where everybody watch or
something. I don't know what you're
doing. That's the time to tell people
everybody watch that. You know,
I hate the little jet bridge though,
man. People get frustrated and people
just don't feel like they moving their
life. You ever like the little steps?
You ever just try to wait to get a
little room to walk cuz there's no point
to keep taking a little step. So, you
just wait. It's always somebody behind
you like you like it's just one step.
They not going to leave us. The the door
is open. They're not going to take off
youm like we going to lose like we going
to miss it.
Them the same off people that come and
ask you has the bus came yet when you
standing on a bus stop.
Evidence me standing here is clearly
that it has not came.
No, I was just sitting here waiting for
you to come back to let YOU KNOW YOU
MISSED THE BUS. YEAH, that's why I was
here.
I don't like TO CALL PEOPLE STUPID, BUT
something's wrong.
I don't like it. I'm getting older. I
see why older people don't have no
patience at all. THEY DON'T HAVE ANY
PATIENCE.
Old people, they don't care. They like,
"I'm leaving here soon. I don't I don't
have time for you. I'm getting there."
AND I'M NOT EVEN OLD.
LIKE, I GOT ON the plane. Like, I DON'T
LIKE WALKING. YOU EVER walk in the
presence of bougess and you feel it
instantly? Like first class is that when
you have to walk past first class, you
feel like you're in the pres like you
feel like a peasant. You like I'm just
trying to get the coach. Ain't trying to
bother nobody. How y'all doing up here?
Oh, it's nice up here. It's well lit.
That's so nice. Oh man. Look like two
people can SIT IN YOUR CHAIR. THAT'S a
nice comfortable chair. Oh, y'all got
your refreshments. So you got juice. Oh,
this is nice.
Just a peasant going to sit in coach.
ain't trying to bother nobody.
I hate doing this character in front of
white people, too.
Makes me feel like a slave. I don't like
it. I'm not.
One time, you know how you you know how
you have to wait in line cuz people are
taking all day to put their stuff in the
overhead bin. So, you get kind of stuck
in first class if you're you know, see
this in coach. The people in first
class, they get uncomfortable. You ever
see them like being fidgety? They be
like when they start looking back like
what's the hold up? Like what's going
on? This lady was like what's going on?
Is something happening back there? And
one lady clenched onto her purse like I
was going to take it.
And she like
I'm mad for two reasons. I'm mad. First
reason is I can still take it.
I can still TAKE IT. YOU'RE NOT THAT
STRONG.
THIS LITTLE QUINCH AIN'T GOING TO STOP
MY WHOLE YANK FROM YOU.
What is wrong with you?
SECOND THING IS WHERE I'MMA GO.
I HAD TO WAIT IN THIS LITTLE LINE
TO GET TO HERE. I'MMA TAKE YOUR PURSE
AND GO SIT IN MY SEAT.
I HAD TO GET HALFWAY NAKED JUST TO GET
TO THIS POINT. ARE YOU STUPID?
HOW WOULD THAT LOOK BE A BLACK MAN?
ROBERT, GIVE ME YOUR PURSE. GIVE THIS A
COACH PURSE. THIS BELONG IN THE BACK.
ANYWAY,
YOU GOT SOME PROBLEMS, COME HOLL AT ME.
I'M IN 34 C
ALL the way in the back by the toilet.
Stop looking at me.
Hey, could you just leave the room and
over here B? I don't want to put my new
purse up there. Yeah. Yeah. They giving
them to black people in the front. You
want your a purse?
I'm
a
I'm aware of stereotypes, but as a black
person or whatever race you represent,
when you go into the world, you
represent that race. Asian people
pressure when you driving.
It's pressure. You like, I GOT TO DO
GREAT.
Mexican people, you got to learn how to
speak your language. You can't be your
your culture and don't know your
language. You ever talk to Mex, they
don't know how to speak Spanish. You
like sad.
White people, I don't know what y'all
is. I don't know what your stereotype
is. Y'all got good stereotypes. Like
good credit, own everything.
I don't really know what your credit is.
I mean, what your thing is.
I'll tell you later. I have to think
about it.
But I don't like I don't like and
everything. There's there's there's
things in life that's built just to make
you feel less than. Like it's literally
put in place to make you feel less than.
First class is that. First class is
that. It is. What is it? They got the
little sheet. Why is it there? You know
the little sheet that separates you from
first class. It ain't no secret what's
going on UP THERE. YOU KNOW WHAT'S going
on there. I CAN SMELL WHEN YOU EATING.
DON'T YOU SMELL IT WHEN THEY GET THEIR
LITTLE FOOD? YOU SMELL IT. IT BE YOU BE
HUNGRY. THEY GET YOU SOME PRETZELS. YOU
DON'T WANT NO PRETZELS. I WANT THIS.
What they eating UP THERE? I WANT THAT.
And the and the the the the flight
attendant, the worst first class, they
always a little bougie, too. They don't
just shed the sheath.
Pay attention. They look to coach to let
you know you don't belong on this side
of the plane.
Hi, how are you? get to see you
like I'm going to come up there when I
get my money together.
I didn't get to reply first class a few
times.
I tried to beat them.
People was like standing there. I was
like, "What's going on? What's going on?
Why is he still here?"
I didn't have a purse, but I would have
clutched on to it, too.
This white man is going to steal my
purse.
These people I you know
that's funny.
I I I'm as a comedian, I travel by
myself a lot. And when I travel by
myself, it's the worst when I get the
middle seat. The middle seat is the
worst. And people don't talk about the
middle seat because the middle seat, you
don't have your own armrest. You share
both armrest with both strangers that
you do not know. So if you have a
problem with touching, you're going to
get over it really fast,
right? And and and when you sit there,
you got to be polite like you like them.
You go, "How you doing? How you doing?"
Then you got to argue like, "Give me
some armrests, please." You got to hurry
up, find your space, and stay there or
they'll miss you. You got to stay there
the whole fight. As soon as you move,
THEY GO THERE LIKE, "AH, NOW I GOT TO
FLY the rest of the flight with my arms
in my lap. This is uncomfortable for
five hours.
One time I got on a plane was two big
football players, big guys like you." I
looked at them, I was like, "Listen, I'm
leaning I'm sleeping on one of y'all's
shoulders.
That's just what's happening. You're
going to have to accept it. I'm not
sitting straight up for 5 hours. So, I
got to go to sleep and I have nowhere to
lean. When you lean, you know, when you
got the window, you can lean on the
window. You can lean out the aisle. Me,
I got to sleep on one of y'all.
Can I Can I borrow your shoulder for a
minute, please?
And I don't know if y'all know like, but
when you have the window seat, you're
the king or the queen of the row. You
know why? Because you get to tell
whether it can be somebody can look out
the window or not.
>> You ever be looking out the window and
they just shut it in YOUR FACE LIKE
YOU OFFENDED, BUT YOU CAN'T SAY NOTHING.
You talking to people, you didn't want
to. He He seemed like he wanted to look
out the window. I guess he don't want to
look out the window. Okay, cool. Don't
worry about it. You start talking to
people. Yeah. I guess he don't want to
see us take off. You saw the takeoff.
It's really nice when you You see?
Yeah. He don't want to see it. That's
all good.
People be funny acting, don't they? They
be getting all bougie cuz they got the
window seat. You know, they think they
God. Let there be light. Nope. They cut
it off, don't they?
Well, I got a couple Joe Biden jokes we
can get into because this is this is
going to be about it with me and Joe
Biden jokes. I think we pretty much come
to the end of our run here,
but still got a couple left for you
guys. And I'm sure you're not fans, so
this should work.
I've never talked to my son about his
business ever.
Well, that makes you a bad dad.
So, um, Joe is, uh, you know, he's, uh,
getting a little up there. And, you
know, at the end, I think they wanted
him to stay on the prompter, right?
Because when he got off the prompter, he
got into trouble. But, even when he
stayed on the prompter, he got into
trouble.
Remember that speech? Four more years.
Pause.
THAT'S NOT JOE'S FAULT. SOMEONE put the
word pause on the prompter.
If it's on the prompter, he's saying it.
That's where he's at. Okay. He's in the
full Ron Burgundy stages of life.
He'd be like, uh, we hold these truths
to be self-evident.
Samsung.
They got into trouble because he stayed
on too long and it didn't give Camala
enough time to prepare to run for the
presidency and people are angry at Joe
for not dropping out earlier.
I had a surefire way to get him to drop
out early and never go for his second
term, but nobody would listen to me. All
I needed to do is get three or four
people from his inner circle together.
And I'd go, "You don't want this
daughtering old fool running for a
second term, do you?" And they'd go,
"No,
no, no. But he's not going to listen to
us. He's doing it anyway.
But just listen to me. Get on the same
page. This is going to work. When he
says, "I'm running for a second term,"
you say, "But this is your second term."
And he'd be like, "Get out of here, you
dogface, LION PONY SOLDIER BOY."
HE GOES, "SIR, this is your second
term." And he goes, "No, it's not." He
goes, "Sir, with all due respect, do you
think you could have screwed the country
up this badly in three years? Come on.
That's a seven-year project right there.
Come on.
You're bad. You're not Jimmy Carter bad.
Okay,
get over yourself.
Poor Jimmy Carter wasn't in office for
44 years, but every once in a while when
a really bad president would come down
the pike, he'd have to turn on the news
and see Shan Hannity's fat heads
going, "We haven't seen this kind of
gross incompetence
since Jimmy Carter."
Jimmy Carter sitting home going, "I
build houses for black people. Leave me
out of this.
He uh he uh had a little issue with his
dog too. Commander, remember uh remember
commander was biting everyone at the
White House and so they had to have the
dog removed. And I was picturing a scene
where a couple Secret Service agents
were just standing outside the Oval
Office and Joe was saying goodbye to
commander for the last time. And the one
Secret Service guy turned to the other
guy and said, "You think they're going
to put him down?"
The other guy went, "I don't know. Well,
what are they going to do with the dog?"
You guys remember about 20 years ago
when George W. Bush was given that
presser in Iraq and that guy threw the
shoes at him from the back of the room.
He pulled his shoe off and he fired a
strike. Just a fast ball right over the
plate and W was like pop.
Then he pulled a second shoe off a
second later and he fired another strike
right over the plate. He was like boom
pop.
And I thought, man, yeah, that was
pretty regal. He didn't flail. He didn't
turn. He didn't do anything. He just
slipped both those loafers.
Tassel. Tassel.
And I thought, I miss those days
because you throw a shoe at Joe Biden,
you will kill the man.
You throw a shoe at Joe Biden, he's
going to be the ratunda on Sunday and
you'll be in Levvenworth for the rest of
your life. And I don't even think it
would take a dress shoe.
I think one wellplaced slipper,
one of Mike Lindell's, rugged yet
handsome.
But I was watching that tape of the guy
throwing the shoe and he was in the back
of an auditorium. He was like 50 feet
away. Pulled one shoe off, fired it, and
then he pulled the next one off on the
run and fired another strike right over
the plate. And I was like, "Look,
you may disagree with that guy
politically, but he had a cannon for an
arm.
Give him his due, man. That guy played
ball, right? And I was like, that guy
played ball in high school. I used to
play baseball. I was like, okay, that
guy played little league, pony league,
probably some high school ball. Cuz you
don't pick that throwing motion up in
your 40s. That's from when you're a
little tikeke. You know, I was like,
yeah, he definitely grew up playing
ball. And I was like, whoa, whoa, whoa,
wait a second. It's Iraq. It's the
Middle East. They don't play baseball
there. They play soccer. They kick the
ball. They don't throw the ball. I was
like, "Where did that guy get that
magnificent throwing motion?"
Oh, he's been stoning women since he was
six.
He was probably his village's champion
stoner of women. THEY WOULD GO TO him
when he was a lad. They'd go to his hut
and be like, "Hhabib,
we've taught some lady reading.
Yeah, bring your gravel."
I had a whole life where this guy worked
out. I figured he got recruited to Hamas
right out of high school.
Had an injury. Had to get the Tommy
Jihad surgery during the off season.
They kicked him down to Triple A. ISIS
picked him up. He flamed out.
Never saw the show.
>> One of the biggest red flags, fellas, is
a woman that volunteers you for street
fights.
Y'all know what I'm talking about.
That woman that overreacts,
overestimates your abilities. Now you
fighting five guys by yourself.
I know. That's why me and my ex are not
together now. She booked me for a fight
at the AMC theater for a 4:30 show of
Spider-Man.
I didn't know I'm getting popcorn. Out
of nowhere, I HEAR MY HUSBAND DON'T PLAY
THAT MESS.
WELL, I'm her boyfriend. I don't know
who she talking about.
Can I get four more squirts of butter,
please?
Then I heard he was trained in the
military. I'm like, ma'am, I was a cook
in the military. What are we talking
about?
I was trained to put gravy on biscuits.
You hear me?
You get shot in FRONT OF ME, YOU KNOW
WHAT I'M QUALIFIED TO DO? DON'T DIE,
SOLDIER. Cuz today's soup specials
is tomato fist and clam chowders.
Uh-oh. He leaving. Get it to go box. He
leaving. Get it to go box.
I need to understand.
>> Technically, I'm a highly skilled Waff
House employee. That's what I am.
They've never went to break up a fight.
They might get in them, but they're not
breaking up y'all fights. The most a
Waffle House employee would do while you
getting scrambled across the floor. Hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey. Do you want wheat or
white bread with your grits?
YOU WANT STRAWBERRY OR GRAPE JELLY? HOLD
ON. Now
she tried to set me up. She talking
about he did two tours in Iraq. Yeah.
For a chili cook off. Who
you saw me PACK PACKING THE PAPRIKA. YOU
SAW IT. I WAS LIKE, "HAND ME THE BLACK
PEPPER. I'M GOING TO KILL THESE BOYS
over there. I'm about to kill it.
I'm about to get the best
tilapia soup ever."
I like that we can come out here and
enjoy life. Cuz let me tell you
something. People argue about silly
things. People online arguing whether we
are ready for free healthcare.
I don't think we ready for free
healthcare.
But I will tell you this, we'll be ready
for free healthcare when we're ready to
fight for it the same way we fought for
the Popeye's chicken sandwich.
I don't know if y'all remember, but
people died over that deep fat fried
yogurt. It was embarrassing.
We made international news with spicy
mayo on our lips. Did y'all see it?
I know what to do. It's not like
Popeye's is the best at customer service
cuz as soon as you walk in,
y'all don't cook at your house.
You pass five Bojangles, three churches.
You like, I'm so sorry I showed up
today. That's my fault.
Best customer service in the food
service industry.
>> Chick-fil-A. Exactly. Chick-fil-A. She
whispered it like somebody in Popeyes is
here tonight. WHO SAID CHICK-FIL-A?
STAND UP.
Show yourself.
I know. Look, I I used to work at
Popeye's. That was the first place I
learned how to box at.
Cuz when they run after that chicken,
you got to know how TO SLIP A JAB and
parry it to the left. I done caught A
FEW STRIKES. UH OH, SHIRLEY, I see you
in the mood today.
Don't get me wrong, Popeye's takes
pride. They have pride. They take pride
in telling you what they out of and
don't have.
As soon as you go, I like to have a
number five.
WE OUT OF FRIES, THIGHS, WINGS, and
pies.
and employees
and rice. YOU CAN GET THE BEANS THOUGH.
We still got the red beans. You want
that?
Go to Chick-fil-A. They take care of
you. I don't even go for the food. I go
for the therapy session.
They greet you. Come on in. How your
kids doing? Matthew, Mark, and Luke.
They don't fry chicken. They baptizing.
You want a number seven
in the name of the father and the son.
HALLELUJAH.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR HANDS, MALACHI? I DON'T
NEED THESE HANDS.
I ain't taking care of you. They mess up
your order, you're not scared to return
it,
are you? You're not. They mess up your
order, guess what they going to do? pray
with you about it. We did what? Grab my
hands.
We go wrong. Father, forgive us for
forsaking their meal. Father,
it's a guy in the back of him CATCHING
THE SPIRIT. YES, LORD.
Go to Popeye's. You terrified to return
your order. You are scared. Even if you
have every right to. You open that bag,
you're like, "Ah,
I didn't order a peanut butter and jelly
sandwich, but you know what?
I'm good. I'm good. It came with a
Capri, son. You know what? This is a
sack lunch, but you know what? I do need
to go on a field trip. I'll just go
ahead and take my bag and go by my
business. I'll just take my bag and go.
There was a time we couldn't even cough
like that. That was back to back. That
was a concerning cough.
I don't know if y'all remember a time
where you only got one cough per row and
that was it. If you felt A TICKLE IN
YOUR THROATS,
YOU HAD TO GRAB IT and massage it out.
Haha.
Please don't judge me. Please don't
judge me. Please don't judge me.
Sir, it leads to concerns.
At one point, news so scary, we watched
to see how people cough. Like a deer
caught in headlights. As soon as we
heard,
I saw somebody at Applebees grab their
chest, lean forward, and cough. I said,
"Oh, that's the Delta variant right
there."
You know, it's bad when you cough and
your knees move up.
There goes another one. Somebody done
call something.
Chick-fil-A
calls you by your name, not the number
on your receipt. Psychologically, that
shows that they appreciate you. And they
want you to know that they appreciate
you.
Not McDonald's.
They still call you by the digits on
your receipt like an inmate.
We got an order for Mick and May. 695787
cell block 4. Are you here?
Speed.
McDonald's is religious. Religious too.
I don't know if y'all know that. They
believe spare the rod spoil the patron.
Which is why if you get out of line,
they will discipline their customers on
sites. Have you seen it? What's the last
viral fight video that went viral? is
where a customer threw fries and a drink
at the manager. You know what the
manager threw? A whole blender. Look it
up.
It was still plugged up to THE WALL.
YOU GOT TO BE angry if you throw a
blender while it's making a McFlurry.
You
I'm like the one time the shake machine
is working.
You use it TO BEAT A CUSTOMER, THE
INSTRUCTIONS SAY BLENDS.
She hiked her legs like she was pitching
FOR THE BRAIDS. YEAH. AH,
you can still hear the cookies grinding.
I said that's got to be from Amazon.
That ain't t-mood. That ain't
got to be from Amazon. That's not
Wish.com. That's Amazon.
I can smell the cookies in the air. M.
That smells good. That's going to be
good when it lands on her face.
Chick-fil-A got this thing where if the
lines get long in the drive-thru, they
come to your vehicle. Did you know that?
>> They met me at the stoplight.
And when it turned green, guess what
they did? Ran beside the car. So you got
an order for number three and four.
Was that a Toyota Prius?
I'm like, this man is good. Okay. Sherry
Richardson, was that a Volvo?
We did a lot of driving in Montana. And
I after about two days, I looked at her.
I said, "You know, this is sad, but
we're at a point in our marriage where
every conversation we have turns into a
game of charades. We honestly can't
remember a thing. We really can't. It's
just it's a game show. We just start
guessing and going, "No, that she'll
say, "I saw that guy you worked with in
New York on TV the other night." And
I'll go, "Oh, yeah. What guy was that?"
And she'll go, "You know that guy." I
go, "No, I don't. That's why I'm asking
you. You brought it up." And then it
just starts, you know, uh, you know, was
it New York City? I don't know. New York
City. Well, Buffalo, Rochester, S. I
don't know. It was New York. I go, okay,
help me out. What did he look like?
Well, he was a white guy. Well, that
narrows it down, sweetheart. Oh my god.
Was he tall? Short? Well, your height,
so 6', 61. Oh, he wasn't that tall. Then
he's not my height.
Goes on for five more minutes. We never
come up with a name. She drifts off and
looks out the window until the next game
show.
Now she's using Alexa to fill in her
memory problems. I mean, it really is.
I'm not kidding you. I'll hear her
reminders all day coming out of Alexa.
Reminder for Tammy, you know, tomatoes
on the grocery list. You know, reminder
for Tammy, 2:00 doctor's and my favorite
one, reminder for Tammy at dinner
tonight. Faint interest in Jeff's golf
story.
I'm not kidding. Anybody got an Alexa?
She's now beginning to chime in our
conversations as if she's a member of
our family.
Tammy, we brought Tammy brought up her
friend Alice. Apparently, Alice saw me
at the airport and waved at me. And
Tammy says, "You completely ignored
her." And I said, "I didn't even see
Alice." And Alexa goes, "Should I order
Sea Alice for Jeff?"
Nobody's even talking to you, lady. Come
on.
You know where this AI is headed. You
know where it's headed. Your wife is
going to say something like, "Don't
forget we have dinner with the Johnson's
tomorrow night." And you're going to
say, "I'm not eating with the Johnson's.
I don't like them." And she's going to
go, "You agreed to this." And you say,
"I would never have agreed to that." And
Alexa will go, "Jeff, you agreed to
dinner with the Johnson 17 days, 12
hours, and 7 minutes ago."
And then she'll say, "Tammy, would you
like me to play back the conversation?"
But you know what's coming after that?
What's coming after that?
Yeah,
my living room lights are connected to
Alexa. So, I mean it we have a we have a
nighttime ritual. Tammy says, "I'm going
to bed." That's she just stands up and
goes, "I'm going to bed." And I Okay, I
got about 10 or 15 minutes. It takes her
that long to put the creams and oils on.
So, it's just So, anyway, I got to close
up the house. So, I'll say, "Alexa, turn
off light one. Alexa, turn off light
two. Alexa, and then I'll I'll set our
alarm and I'll go to bed." Now, we live
in the country. We live rural Tennessee.
our Wi-Fi is just not all that good. So
there's nights I say, "Alexa, turn off
light one." And she starts this mantra.
I'm unable to connect right now. You
need to get your router. And she starts
giving me directions on routers and
things. And I just, you know, wait for
her to stop talking and I'll say,
"Alexa, turn off light one. Am I able to
connect right now?" And sometimes it
takes four or five times to get her to
turn out the light. Now, I know a lot of
you are thinking, "Hey, why don't you
just walk over and turn off the light?"
I thought about it, but then, you know,
I pay her to do it, so that's why I'm
not going to
What are you? Gen Z Alexa.
So, one night, one night I got to close
up shop. I got to go to the bathroom and
I tell Tammy to close up the house. And
this is what I hear. I come out of my
living room. She Tammy says, "Alexa,
turn off light one." She goes, "I'm
going to be able to connect right now."
And Tammy interrupts her. Don't even let
her finish. She just interrupts her.
Alexa, be quiet. I'm talking to you. And
Alexa's going, And now Alexa, her she's
just swimming. She's just I mean it's
just jabber jabber. And Tam's going, "BE
QUIET, ALEXA. I'M TALKING TO YOU NOW.
SHUT UP."
And then Tammy loses her mind. She's
just going, "Alexa, ALEXA, ALEXA." I GOT
to run. I put my hands on her shoulder.
Baby, take a breath. You see that blue
light spinning around and around and
around? That's her brain.
Let the BLUE LIGHT GO OUT.
I KNOW YOU IMAGINE THESE TWO TECH giants
standing together in the living room,
but yeah, let the blue light go out. So,
light went out. I said, "Alexa, turn off
light one." Light one went out. I said,
"Sweetheart, you got to know how to talk
to a woman."
>> I filmed an entire comedy special called
Banned from Karate. Okay. Yeah.
In that comedy special, uh, I get banned
from Karate Forever for knocking out a
fairly old gentleman at a karate
tournament, uh, when I should not have.
Now, I thought I should name an entire
special banned from karate cuz karate is
the craziest place I could possibly be
banned from. Right. That is until I was
banned from an entire continent. So, I
was like, "Oh, what?" Yeah. Yeah. I was
banned from the country of Australia.
So, I really jumped the gun on thinking
I had the best version of a band thing.
I guess I have to have two albums called
Band from I don't know. I don't know.
So, how that happened is crazier than
you could ever imagine. So, I scheduled
shows in the country of Australia. They
sold. I was very excited to go. I went
to get a work visa. I applied. Country
of Australia ghosts me. Weird, right? I
send my lawyer like, "Hey, can I get a
work visa?" My lawyer looks into it. The
country of Australia's like, "He can't
have one." My lawyer's like, "What?
Why?" And they go, "Shane can't have a
work visa because he's a political
extremist."
What?
I was like, "If someone been publishing
my dream journal, how would they know?
How would they know?
How they would know is crazier than you
could ever imagine." Okay, you guys know
how we have a president right now. The
guy with the hair. You know him? Okay.
Well, we used to have a different
president, the one before him. He was
sleepier. Okay, that was him. We all
remember that was his deal. Before he
fell asleep, he did a bunch of stuff.
And one of those things we'll call
spying. Okay,
he used an organization called the
Federal Bureau of Investigation. Okay.
and he decided to spy on a few groups of
Americans he thought might be up to
stuff. Okay. And one of those groups is
a group of people we'll call Catholics.
Okay. All right. Now,
I had happened to convert to Catholicism
a couple of years ago right when this
was going on. And then I immediately
started going to something called the
Latin mass. For those of you who don't
know what that is, that's church on hard
mode. Okay. That is Yes. That is the
Elden Ring of Church. Okay.
Similar vibes, similar music,
immaculate. No notes. Okay.
So,
I go I go there and the government's
like, "Whoa, check this guy out doing
the craziest thing you can do when
you're Catholic. We will watch him."
Here is the thing about me. If you
observe me over a long enough period of
time, I'll build a bomb. I WILL I'LL DO
IT. I WILL DO THAT. It's a thing I do.
Okay. So, they were watching me and I
built a bomb. NOW,
it's s I'LL BE REAL.
I'll be real with you. It sounds like
I'm telling on myself,
but I'm not. Okay, two things. Firstly,
that bomb was for joy. Okay, that was
that was a bomb between me and the boys
only. All right, NO ONE ELSE WAS
SUPPOSED TO KNOW ABOUT THIS BOMB. All
right, the second thing, I am from Utah
where bombs are legal. Okay. HEY, HEY,
COME ON NOW. THAT'S WHAT'S UP.
THE greatest state in these United
States. OKAY, SO
I am from the middle of nowhere in
central Utah, a place most people don't
know exists. Okay, so I'm out in the
desert walking around with my friends,
which is what we do out there. That's
pretty much it. All right, so we're
walking around the desert and we found
an abandoned car and me and my friends
were like, "So we're going to blow this
car up, right?"
So, we all make the decision as a unit
that we're going to blow this car
skyhigh. Then we realize, oh man, 20 lbs
of tannerite isn't funny enough. Okay?
For those of you who don't know what
that is, let me just tell you, IT'S
ENOUGH EXPLOSIVE. OKAY? IT'S ENOUGH,
but it's not funny enough. So, we make a
plan. You know, we're all adults. We
live in different places. So, we're
going to gather back up where I'm from
to blow up this car. Now, you have to
coordinate with other adults who have
children and families and wives. We all
got stuff going on. How do you
coordinate building a bomb as a team?
You got to start a group chat. Okay. So,
yes.
WELL, IN THE MIDST of being spied on by
the FBI,
me and my idiot redneck friends were
like, "So, we're going to call the group
chat the bomb. Okay.
We're gonna we're GONNA REPEATEDLY TALK
ABOUT THE BOMB LIKE IT'S A member of the
friend group. Okay,
we're gonna reference it a lot. We're
talking about supplies we are gathering
for the bomb. Okay,
now here's where IT GETS CRAZY. AT ONE
POINT, THIS becomes such a bit between
all of us that we are doing things like
saying hi to the FBI agent, reading the
chat.
WE'RE WE'RE DOING THE BIT,
but he's in the chat.
Can you imagine how much damage is being
done to his mental health
to BE TO BE ASSIGNED TO SPY ON ME? VERY
CLEARLY AN IDIOT, RIGHT?
He's like, his bosses are like, "This is
a loweffort case. He's a comedian. He's
not up to anything. Just spy on him.
Tell us what you see." And then he has
to be on his computer like the group
chat the bomb. And then at one point,
one of my friends is like, "Found two
sticks of dynamite."
To which we all reply, "Hello, FBI agent
reading this."
And the FBI agent's like, "Do they know
I'm here?"
And they're just cool with it. Like,
WHAT? IT WOULD BE LIKE if you went duck
hunting for your very first time and you
were standing there chilling and a duck
flew down and swam up to you and was
just like, "Yo, kill me right now."
Like, I DON'T EVEN WANT TO BE HERE
ANYMORE. You'd be doing us both a favor.
You would be standing there with YOUR
FRIENDS LIKE, "DO I SHOOT HIM OR DO WE
GET HIM HELP? LIKE, WHAT IS GOING ON?
WHAT DO I DO?" THAT FBI agent had to be
like, "Do I let them get away with
this?" Like, "What is What do I do?"
So, we blew up the car. It was awesome,
right? We loved it. We loved it. And
then Australia is like, "You can't have
a work visa." And I was like, "Oh, no.
Like, I'm not a political extremist. I'm
just like a dumb guy.
I'm like a redneck. Can I please come
into your country?" And they were like,
"No,
I think you made it worse." You know?
So, we're like, "Can Shane have a work
visa?" This is a huge misunderstanding.
And uh the country of Australia was
like, "You're on a list." Like, there's
no way because I was the back then they
put they they had so many people on
watch lists that they had to make new
different ones. And I was on the baby
terrorist watch list. Okay? I was on the
bottom one watching me. So they're
watching me and the country of Australia
is like, "This guy's on a list. We don't
know about him." So my lawyer's like,
"You're wrong. He's just a weird guy or
whatever." And they're like, "Nah." And
then we're like, "Hey, what can we do to
make you more comfortable? Shane would
like to do whatever it takes to come
perform. Like he's a comedian. This is
totally chill." And the country of
Australia is like, "Okay, yeah, you
could play ball with us. What we need
from you so that you can get your work
visa. We need to get comfortable." They
say the first thing you can do for us,
you can write us a letter apologizing
for last time you were in our country
and you got caught speeding.
Let's all recap what just happened.
The government of Australia is like,
"This guy might be some kind of
religious or political extremist. He
builds bombs. He can't come into our
country." And we were like, "What can we
do to make you feel comfortable?" And
then THEY GO, "APOLOGIZE FOR GOING TOO
FAST." WHAT?
What a very unserious and bad government
they have there.
All right.